Guide to the United Automobile Workers of America, District 65 Photographs, Part I: Negatives PHOTOS.023
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
- Series I. Negatives, Bulk, 1940-1959; 1938-1969 (bulk 1940s-1950s)
  - Subseries I:B - Individuals - 1939-1969
    - Lichtenfeld, Harry [Photographer Feature], Feb 7, 1945 (Negative 26150)
    - Lichtenfeld, Hy - Portrait for Feature on His Anti-Polio Activity [Portrait Feature], Jun 2, 1959 (Negative 29153)
    - Lichtenstein, Sylvia [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 28036)
    - Lichtman, Esther [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 28037)
    - Liebe, Ches Sergeant [Portrait Feature], May 15, 1945 (Negative 28352)
    - Lieberman, Louis [Portrait Feature], May 25, 1950 (Negative 28695)
    - Lieberman, Paul and Ester [Photographer Feature], Jul 21, 1954 (Negative 27285)
    - Lifschitz, Abe of A.S. Beck Shoe - Retiree, Jul 3, 1953 (Negative 11277-11279)
    - Lifschitz, Jessie [Capsule Biography Feature] [Portrait Feature], undated; Jan 10, 1961 (Negative 28039; 29265)
    - Light Brown, Walter [Photographer Feature], Dec 28, 1947 (Negative 26638)
    - Lilienfield, Florence [Photographer Feature], Feb 19, 1946 (Negative 26304)
    - Limuti, Hugo [Portrait Feature], Nov 17, 1952 (Negative 28882)
    - Lindsey, Ella [Photographer Feature], 1953 (Negative 27141)
    - Lion, Emil [Photographer Feature], Apr 28, 1948 (Negative 27476)
    - Lipman, Florence [Photographer Feature], Feb 6, 1946 (Negative 26299)
    - Lipman, Mildred [Photographer Feature], Jul 8, 1946 (Negative 26390)
    - Lipschitz, Anna [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 28040)
    - Lipschutz, Marty [Portrait Feature], Jul 28, 1947 (Negative 29443)
    - Lipschutz, Sol] [Photographer Feature], Jul 10, 1945 (Negative 26214)
    - Lipsky, Sol [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 28041)
    - Lisner, D - Buying a Bond, Oct 24, 1941; Feb 8, 1944 (Negative 798; 1615)
    - Litoff, Sidney [Photographer Feature], Aug 4, 1948 (Negative 26763)
    - Livingston Addresses Textile Strikers, Sep 3, 1946 (Negative 2805-2806)
    - Livingston, David, Arthur Osman & Jack Paley (Histaprut), Nov 10, 1953 (Negative 12001)
    - Livingston, David ["Capsule Biography" feature], May 17, 1948; May 28, 1948; Feb 5, 1950; May 1950; July 8, 1952; undated (Negative 28042-28052)
    - Livingston, David ["Inquiring Photographer" feature], Mar 20, 1946 (Negative 26321-26322)
    - Livingston on Channel 7, Nov 1963 (Negative 22763-22766)
    - Livingston, David ["Portrait" feature], Jan 1942; Sep 21, 1953; Feb 2, 1954; Feb 21, 1955; Jun 26, 1962; Oct 18, 1960 (Negative 941; 29010-29011; 29038; 29052-29053; 29307; 29230)
    - Livingston: Press interviews, Sep 3, 1946 (Negative 2807-2809)
    - Livingston, David, Pvt., Mar 11, 1945 (Negative 2114-2115)
    - Livingston, David, Pvt. - Farewell party, Mar 3, 1944 (Negative 1622-1630)
    - Livingston, David - Voting, Jun 3, 1962; undated (Negative 20230; 29623-29625)
    - Livingston - Meeting of Retired District 65 Members Being Addressed by David Livingston, May 8, 1956 (Negative 14991)
    - Livingston, Mr. & Mrs. D., May 2, 1949 (Negative 5132)
    - Livingston, Madge, Jun 19, 1945 (Negative 2195-2196)
    - Lizotte, Eugene [Photographer Feature], Mar 20, 1946 (Negative 26316)
    - Lo Bianco, Tony, Sergeant [Taft-Hartley repeal], Nov 22, 1948; Nov 3, 1944 (Negative 4686-4687; 28298)
    - Lobe, Jack [Photographer Feature], Apr 2, 1945 (Negative 26176)
    - Local 2 [Photographer Feature], Aug 17, 1949 (Negative 27367)
    - Local 26 Distributive, Processing and Office Workers of America - Anniversary Party, Jun 28, 1952 (Negative 9126-9141)
    - Local 3 Officers, May 13, 1949 (Negative 5994-5999)
    - Local 830 member, Sep 23, 1948 (Negative 29763)
    - Local Officers [Portrait Feature] (1940?), Jul 1930; undated; Jul 1930 (Negative 29922-29949; 29958-29978;)
    - Local Officers 1952 [Portrait Feature] (Negative 29950-29962)
    - Lodolcetta, Vincent [Photographer Feature], Feb 10, 1946 (Negative 26380)
    - Loe, Selany - Feature [retiree?], Dec 2, 1952 (Negative 10025-10032)
    - Loeb, Sammy [Photographer Feature], Sep 29, 1947 (Negative 26607)
    - Loeser Meeting and Interviews, Jan 24, 1952 (Negative 8431-8440)
    - Loeser Workers, Aug 7, 1951 (Negative 7857; 29837-29838)
    - Loeser Workers - 100 Years at Loeser [Portrait Feature], Jul 12, 1950; Dec 7, 1950 (Negative 29813-29815)
    - Logalbo, Joseph [Photographer Feature], undated (Negative 26077)
    - Loheide, Joe [of Stern's] [Portrait Feature], Mar 22, 1949 (Negative 28599)
    - Lomazon, Bill [Photographer Feature], Sep 28, 1950 (Negative 27491)
    - Lombard, Perry [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 28053)
    - Lombardi, Anthony [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 28054)
    - Lombardo, V. of John Stewart Portrait, Jul 1963 (Negative 22112)
    - London, Miriam [Inquiring Photographer Features], Mar 3, 1947; Mar 26, 1947 (Negative 26521-26522)
    - London, Nettie [Photographer Feature], undated (Negative 26076)
    - Loney, Dr. [Portrait Feature], undated (Negative 25137-25138)
    - Lopez, Charles (left) and George (right) [Portrait Feature], Jun 12-13, 1954 (Negative 29047)
    - Lopez, Damocles [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 28055-28056)
    - Lopez, Gilbert, Nov 16, 1945 (Negative 2399)
    - Lopez, John [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 28057)
    - Lopez, Theodore (Candy) [Photographer Feature], Sep 3, 1947 (Negative 26599)
    - Lopos, Victor [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 28058)
    - Lord, Virginia [Photographer Feature], Oct 15, 1953 (Negative 27202)
    - Lorenzo, Albert - Art Winner [Portrait Feature], May 17, 1961 (Negative 29246)
    - Loring, Marcella [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 28059-28060)
    - Loughney, Katherine [Portrait Feature], Feb 26, 1952 (Negative 28814)
    - Lowe, Irma [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 28061)
    - Lowenstein, Isaac [Portrait Feature], Jan 1949 (Negative 28593)
    - Lubart, Allen [Photographer Feature], Nov 27, 1945 (Negative 26275)
    - Lubin, Hy [Portrait Feature], Jun 27, 1945 (Negative 28374)
    - Lucas, Alma [Photographer Feature], Sep 16, 1954 (Negative 27305)
    - Lucci, Gerard [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 28062)
    - Lucci, Louis [Photographer Feature], Nov 2, 1944 (Negative 26107)
    - Luciano, Red, Jul 3, 1942 (Negative 1196)
    - Luding, John [Portrait Feature], Dec 14, 1943 (Negative 28264)
    - Ludwig, John - Retired Member Repairs Toys, Nov 10, 1959 (Negative 17708-17708)
    - Ludwig, John [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 28063)
    - Ludwig, Miriam [Photographer Feature], Aug 19, 1947 (Negative 26586)
    - Lugo, Reuben - Nightclub Singer [Portrait Feature], Feb 24, 1953 (Negative 28945)
    - Luipold, Alfred [of Stern's] [Portrait Feature], Mar 22, 1949 (Negative 28600)
    - Luoghney, Kathryn [Photographer Feature], Mar 9, 1949 (Negative 26896)
    - Lusher, Berne, L.A. [Capsule Biography Feature], Apr 1952 (Negative 28064)
    - Lustgarten, Vera [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 28065)
    - Lusthaus, Abe of Public Service D.M., Jan 18, 1957 (Negative 15623)
    - Lynch, Estelle [Portrait Feature], Jul 28, 1950 (Negative 28709)
    - Lynch, John [Capsule Biography Feature] [Portrait Feature], undated; Apr 7, 1949 (Negative 28066; 28606)
    - Lynette, Jean [Photographer Feature], Nov 2, 1944 (Negative 26108)
    - Lyte, Marcella [Photographer Feature], Feb 7, 1945 (Negative 26149)
    - Mac Anspach, Gerald [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 28067)
    - Mack, Doris [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 28068)
    - Mack, Gerrie and Husband, May 29, 1942 (Negative 1154-1157)
    - MacMahon, Douglas - of Transport Workers Union with Arthur Osman at Stewards Council Meeting, Jan 12, 1943 (Negative 1347)
    - MacOnspack, Gerald [Portrait Feature], Jan 11, 1945 (Negative 28314)
    - MacPherson, Lockland ["Inquiring Photographer" Feature], Jul 6, 1949 (Negative 26990)
    - Macy's Workers Interview [Portrait Feature], Feb 17, 1948 (Negative 29748-29751)
    - Maczuga, Anna [Photographer Feature], undated (Negative 26074)
    - Madden, Lotta [Portrait Feature] - Local 5, Mar 17, 1952 (Negative 28829)
    - Mado Job Trainees, Apr 1963 (Negative 21544-21553)
    - Magasiner, Ray - Bloomingdale's [Portrait Feature], Mar 13, 1952 (Negative 28825)
    - Magulies, Sylvia [Photographer Feature], May 26, 1947 (Negative 26539)
    - Mailman, Harold [Capsule Biography Feature] [Photographer Feature] [Portrait Feature], undated; Oct 29, 1946; Jan 2, 1946 (Negative 28070; 26441; 28457)
    - Maisonave, Raymond [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 28071-28072)
    - Majeski, Charles [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 28073)
    - Makeover, Morris ["Inquiring Photographer" Feature] [Capsule Biography Feature], Nov 27, 1945; undated (Negative 26270; 28074)
    - Maldonado, Rosanna [Portrait Feature], Aug 14, 1952 (Negative 28873)
    - Malley, Annie [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 28075)
    - Mancuso, Edith Receptionist [Portrait Feature], Jan 15, 1945 (Negative 28317)
    - Mandala, Steve - Singer (Gregory) [Made Hit Rock and Roll Record] [Portrait Feature], Jun 27, 1960 (Negative 29187-29189)
    - Mandel, George [Portrait Feature] [Capsule Biography Feature] [Photographer Feature], Apr 21, 1945; undated; Jun 26, 1945 (Negative 28344; 28076; 26208)
    - Mandel, Hy and Sid Kessler [Photographer Feature], Jun 19, 1950 (Negative 27105)
    - Mandell, Oscar [Portrait Feature], Nov 14, 1948 (Negative 28569)
    - Mandes, Herbert [Photographer Feature], Mar 31, 1954 (Negative 27260)
    - Manheim, Phil - [Portrait Features] [Capsule Biography Features], Jun 11, 1943; undated; Feb 15, 1960 (Negative 28252; 28077-28081; 29267; 28079)
    - Mankin, Ernest [Photographer Feature], Jan 1949 (Negative 26838)
    - Mannine, Vito [Photographer Feature], Apr 11, 1950 (Negative 27090)
    - Manning, Irene [Photographer Feature], Aug 21, 1946 (Negative 26401)
    - Manno, Marie [Portrait Feature], Apr 7, 1947 (Negative 29431)
    - Manuel, Mr. and Daughter - Club 65, Oct 12, 1945 (Negative 2341)
    - Marcantonio Madison Square Rally; Marcantonio [?] with Henry Wallace and P. Robeson; Marcantonio, Vito with Esther Letz at Uptown Textile Meeting; Reception; Marcantonio, Vito - Interview, 1949; Oct 23, 1949; Sep 15, 1949; Oct 7, 1947; Sep 19, 1949; Jan 18, 1944 (Negative 5730-5738; 5670-5671; 5508-5510; 3153-3154; 5521-5523; 1608-1609)
    - Marchese, Jean [Photographer Feature], Aug 23, 1944 (Negative 26081)
    - Marcial, Mary [Photographer Feature], Nov 12, 1953 (Negative 27209)
    - Marcus, Dr. J [Portrait Feature], Nov 27, 1945 (Negative 28435)
    - Marcus, Miriam [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 28082)
    - Mardenfeld, Sam - Garment Supply - Fibre Yarn Co. [Capsule Biography Feature], Oct 1958 (Negative 28083)
    - Margolies, Lou - First Vice President Local 144 - Local 144 Executive Board and Dance Committee [Portrait Feature], Dec 7, 1946 (Negative 28559)
    - Margolies, Lou and Maurice Weiss, Manny Alter, (seated: left to right) Ben Berman, Harry Jacobson (standing: left to right) - Dance Committee [Portrait Feature], Dec 7, 1946 (Negative 28564)
    - Margolies, Mary [Photographer Feature], Dec 10, 1947 (Negative 26647)
    - Margolis, Herman [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 28084)
    - Margolis, Lou - That's My Job [Portrait Feature]; [Photographer Feature], 1950; Feb 10, 1946 (Negative 28749; 26378)
    - Margolis, Louis, Feb 10, 1946 (Negative 26378)
    - Marguillo, Sarah [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 28092)
    - Margulies, Lou - Display Local Chairman [Capsule Biography Feature], 1952 (Negative 28085)
    - Margulies, Sylvia [Photographer Feature], Jan 1949 (Negative 26840-26843)
    - Maria, 1949 (Negative 5369-5371)
    - Markham, Margaret [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 28086-28087)
    - Markowitz, Goldie [Photographer Feature], Jun 28, 1954 (Negative 27276)
    - Markowski, Ted [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 28088)
    - Markowski, Valerie [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 28089)
    - Marks, George [Photographer Feature], Oct 16, 1945 (Negative 26257)
    - Marks, Irene [Photographer Feature], Jan 1949 (Negative 26846)
    - Marnet, Lucille [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 28090)
    - Marra, Frances [Photographer Feature], Jul 10, 1948 (Negative 26741)
    - Marsh, Lilly Mae - Charleston, NC [Portrait Feature], Jun 30, 1952 (Negative 28842)
    - Marshall, Louis and Robert Pinto [Photographer Feature], Aug 14, 1950 (Negative 27112)
    - Marshall, Margaret [Portrait Features], Dec 5, 1949; Dec 22, 1949 (Negative 28655; 28661)
    - Marshall, Mary [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 3243)
    - Martin, Carol, Dec 13, 1947 (Negative 3446)
    - Martin, Charles [Photographer Feature], Nov 22, 1944 (Negative 26134)
    - Martinez, Ana, Whose Daughter Morgana Goes to Medical School on C.U. Student Loan [Portrait Feature], Oct 1964 (Negative 29393)
    - Martinez, Dr. Morgana at Kings County Hospital [Portrait Feature], Aug 26, 1968 (Negative 29479-29483)
    - Martinez, Nelson [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 28091)
    - Martino, Jim [Photographer Feature] [Portrait Feature], May 18, 1949; Jan 10, 1945 (Negative 26951-26952; 28313)
    - Martocchia, Linda [Photographer Feature], Feb 15, 1949 (Negative 26871)
    - Maruca, Rose Anne [Photographer Feature], Jul 24, 1946 (Negative 26382)
    - Marx, Joe [Photographer Feature], May 29, 1946 (Negative 26362)
    - Masden, Shirley Nevins [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 28069)
    - Mashioff, Thelma [Photographer Feature], Jul 24, 1946 (Negative 26384)
    - Maslow, Norman [Portrait Features], Jan 10, 1946; Sep 4, 1946 (Negative 28463; 28549)
    - Matarazza, Ralph [Portrait Feature], Jan 10, 1946 (Negative 28462)
    - Matheson - Vin Jamaica [Portrait Feature], Aug 29, 1950 (Negative 28723)
    - Mattarese, Mike at Home - Thanksgiving Feature, Nov 22, 1951 (Negative 8190-8195)
    - Matter, Harry of A. Cohen and Sons - Retiring, Aug 28, 1956 (Negative 15318-15321)
    - Matthews, Alfreda [Photographer Feature], Jan 25, 1950 (Negative 27072)
    - Mauldin, Louis ["Inquiring Photographer" Features], Sep 4, 1946; Apr 8, 1953 (Negative 26408; 27135)
    - Mboya, Tom - Kenyan Labor Leader Visits District 65 [C. Robinson], Aug 31, 1956 (Negative 15313-15314)
    - McAndrews, Helen [Photographer Feature], Jun 7, 1950 (Negative 27102)
    - McArteen, Patrick [Photographer Feature], Jan 8, 1948 (Negative 26655-26656)
    - McBracken, Jean [Photographer Feature], Dec 7, 1949 (Negative 27038-27039)
    - McDermott, Pete - 25-Year Club - Gimbels [Portrait Feature], May 25, 1950 (Negative 28694)
    - McGee, Jim of Schimmel Co. - Weight Lifter Made U.S. Olympic Team, Jun 27, 1960 (Negative 18192-18194)
    - McGovern, Grace [Portrait Feature], Mar 21, 1946 (Negative 28507)
    - McIntyre, Elsie [Photographer Feature], Jul 22, 1947 (Negative 26575)
    - McIntyre, O.E. - Direct Mail Organizer; Anna Matthews and Family, Jan 7, 1956 (Negative 14542-14545)
    - McLean, Robert [Portrait Feature], Nov 15, 1948 (Negative 28580)
    - McLemore, John - Memphis, Tenn. [Capsule Biography Feature], Apr 1952 (Negative 28093)
    - McCarrie, Rose Marie [Portrait Feature], Mar 30, 1948 (Negative 29471)
    - McCauley, Thomas [Photographer Feature], Aug 23, 1944 (Negative 26080)
    - McCrae, Bill [Portrait Feature], Sep 11, 1951 (Negative 28775)
    - McDermott, Pat [of?] Belding - Hemingway, Jul 25, 1945; Mar 1942 (Negative 2228-2229; 1050)
    - McDowell, Alice - at work [Photographer Feature], Oct 19, 1945; May 3, 1946; Oct 4, 1944 (Negative 2360-2361; 2621; 26100)
    - McDuffie, Jean [Photographer Feature], Dec 5, 1953 (Negative 27218)
    - McGill, Frank [Photographer Feature] [Portrait Feature], Aug 30, 1948; Jun 15-16, 1953 (Negative 26783; 26787)
    - McGill, 'Pat', Sergeant, Mar 3, 1944 (Negative 1621)
    - McGurran, Mary [Photographer Feature], Mar 20, 1946 (Negative 26320)
    - McIntyre, Elsie [Portrait Feature], Jul 25, 1947 (Negative 29442)
    - McIntyre, Peggy [of Stern's] [Portrait Feature], Mar 22, 1949 (Negative 28603)
    - McKeon, Mary and James Samsar [Photographer Feature], Jun 7, 1950 (Negative 27100)
    - McMann, Ann A&S Worker [Portrait Feature], Apr 25, 1955 (Negative 29056)
    - McMullin, Al - #8 Pitcher - Garment Area [Portrait Feature], Aug 5, 1953; Jul 28, 1952 (Negative 29004; 28866)
    - McNeil, Cliff [Photographer Feature], Nov 22, 1944 (Negative 26129)
    - McShane, Augusta - Contest Winner, Feb 19, 1945 (Negative 2087)
    - Meah, Sona ["Inquiring Photographer" Features], Apr 2, 1946; Jul 21, 1954 (Negative 26327; 27288)
    - Mears, Ed - Rochelle, Ill. [Capsule Biography Feature], Apr 1952 (Negative 28094)
    - Medaer, Leon [Photographer Feature], Feb 26, 1945 (Negative 26162)
    - Medical Plan Stewards of New Jersey, Feb 26, 1953 (Negative 10253)
    - Medina, Christobal - Textile Member Who Sings, Composes And Makes Records, Nov 25, 1958 (Negative 16945-16946)
    - Medwin, Alma - Poses for District 65 - Customer Service [Store] - Advertisement, Nov 14, 1956; Dec 11, 1958 (Negative 16969-16971)
    - Meegan [Portrait Feature], Sep 28, 1960 (Negative 29229)
    - Meegan, John, 1950 (Negative 7392)
    - Meegan, John - Local 2 [Portrait Feature], Jan 7, 1950 (Negative 28667-28668)
    - Meigide, Doug - E-1 Meeting; Farewell Party; Wedding; Lieutenant Doug Meigide and Al Evanoff, Helen Friedman - E-1 Organizers, Oct 1942; Oct 24, 1942; May 29, 1942; Aug 19, 1943 (Negative 1294-1295; 1149-1153; 1519)
    - Meinel, Edith [Photographer Feature], 1953 (Negative 27177)
    - Meisler, George [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 28095)
    - Meli, Robert [Photographer Feature], Feb 3, 1948 (Negative 26678-26679)
    - Mende, Bob and Irv Baldinger [UV Editor, Mende novelist, 65'er] [Portrait Feature], Feb 3, 1949 (Negative 28594)
    - Mende, Bob Portrait [Portrait Feature], Nov 19, 1951 (Negative 28801)
    - Mende, Sam [Portrait Feature], Jun 1962 (Negative 29291-29292)
    - Mendez, Tony [Portrait Features], Jun 27, 1962; Nov 19, 1962 (Negative 29303-29304; 29321)
    - Mendoza, Frances ["Inquiring Photographer" Features], Aug 14, 1950; Jul 10, 1948 (Negative 27116; 26747)
    - Mendoza, Jacinto - Lerner Member Whose Severed Arm Was Restored, Sep 1964 (Negative 23354-23361)
    - Menendez, Jose V. [Photographer Feature], Jun 26, 1946 (Negative 26371)
    - Merceron, Henri Portrait [Portrait Feature], Jan 23, 1961 (Negative 29241)
    - Met-Ella Jones [Photographer Feature], Jan 4, 1950 (Negative 27082-27083)
    - Meyer, Gus of Hecht's [Portrait Feature], Nov 12, 1945 (Negative 28426)
    - Meyer, Seymour [Photographer Feature], Sep 16, 1954 (Negative 27306)
    - Meyerowitz, Lou [Portrait Feature], Nov 3, 1945 (Negative 28425)
    - Meyers, Mervin - Cedar Rapids, Iowa [Capsule Biography Feature], Apr 1952 (Negative 28096)
    - Meyerson, Harry - First Retired District 65 Steward at Council Meeting, Nov 7, 1956 (Negative 15517)
    - Meyerson, Harry [Photographer Feature], Nov 26, 1946 (Negative 26462)
    - Micallefi, Chas [Portrait Feature], Jun 4, 1945 (Negative 28359)
    - Michaels, Selma [Photographer Feature], Dec 17, 1946 (Negative 26485)
    - Michaelson, William [Capsule Biography Features], undated; Sep 28, 1953; Feb 13, 1961; Mar 27, 1963; Jun 19, 1962; Jun 27, 1962; Jul 1963; Oct 20, 1960 (Negative 22118; 20797; 9301; 22118; 25167-25168; 28097-28099; 29013-29014; 29232; 29301-29302; 29592;)
    - Mickey, Amelia [Photographer Feature], Sep 17, 1947 (Negative 26606)
    - Migliorino, Connie [Photographer Feature], Nov 2, 1944 (Negative 26104)
    - Milgram, Harry - Softball All-Star - Second Baseman [Portrait Feature], Jul 21, 1952 (Negative 28857-28857)
    - Miller, Bella of Stern's [Portrait Feature], Nov 5, 1952 (Negative 28880)
    - Miller, Bertha [Photographer Feature], Jun 24, 1947 (Negative 26561)
    - Miller, Frank [Photographer Feature], Mar 2, 1949 (Negative 26880-26881)
    - Miller, George - Hearn's [Portrait Feature]; Roller Derby Skater Portrait, Nov 19, 1951; Aug 1963 (Negative 28794; 22406)
    - Miller, Jack - U.J. A. Scroll [Portrait Feature] [United Jewish Appeal], Feb 4, 1946; Jun 13, 1945 (Negative 28479; 28362)
    - Miller, Paula [Photographer Feature], Jun 26, 1946 (Negative 26368)
    - Miller, Selma [Portrait], undated (Negative 24988-24989)
    - Millet, Wilhelm - Garment Area Singer [Portrait Feature], Apr 28, 1952; Feb 13, 1952 (Negative 28832; 8490)
    - Millman, Frank [Portrait Feature], Apr 23, 1946 (Negative 28525)
    - Millman, Jack [Photographer Feature], Nov 22, 1944 (Negative 26132)
    - Millstone, Alex [Portrait Feature], Mar 11, 1945 (Negative 28333)
    - Milo, John [Photographer Feature], Apr 14, 1948 (Negative 27466)
    - Milovsky, Neal [Portrait Feature], Feb 25, 1946 (Negative 28489)
    - Minall, Larry [Portrait Feature], Dec 27, 1945 (Negative 28454)
    - Miniz, Agridino Portrait [Portrait Feature], Sep 1, 1960 (Negative 29218)
    - Minton, Max [Photographer Feature], Nov 12, 1953 (Negative 27213)
    - Mintz, Norman [Portrait Feature], Nov 8, 1948 (Negative 29331-29332)
    - Mintz, Sylvia [Photographer Feature], Oct 11, 1948 (Negative 26807)
    - Miraglia, Frank [Photographer Feature], Oct 29, 1946 (Negative 26442)
    - Mirell, Mrs. - American Women's Voluntary Services, Aug 1942 (Negative 1233)
    - Mirell, S.S., Lieutenant [Portrait Feature], Aug 22, 1944 (Negative 28292)
    - Mirell, Stut Lee, Jun 7, 1943 (Negative 1479)
    - Mirojnick, Nancy [Photographer Feature], 1953 (Negative 27179)
    - Mirror Beautiful Child Contest Winner - Daughter of Lucas Solana, Apr 18, 1953 (Negative 10640-10645; 10641-10647)
    - Miscato, Vince [Portrait Feature], Aug 8, 1949 (Negative 28619)
    - Misell, Lee, Ensign [Portrait Feature], Jan 5, 1945 (Negative 28312)
    - Mishkin, Barnie H. [Photographer Feature], Dec 3, 1946 (Negative 26466)
    - Mitchell, Dorothy [Photographer Feature], Jul 21, 1954 (Negative 27286)
    - Mitchell, Thomas and Family, Feb 13, 1961 (Negative 29592)
    - Mitchell, Tom (Portrait) [Portrait Feature], Jan 14, 1953 (Negative 28905)
    - Mittleman, Alex [Portrait Feature [Poster- CIO Political Action Committee In Our Draft ] - 11-time donor, Oct 9, 1944 (Negative 28296)
    - Mojico, Julio Full Length Portrait [Portrait Feature], Aug 1959 (Negative 29167)
    - Molbogot, Milton and Norman Hirsch [Photographer Feature], Apr 7, 1949 (Negative 26914-26916)
    - Molica, J. (Placement Director Training Program) and Fernando Pinon and John Gross [of Textile Local] Checking Graduate Eligibility for Jobs, undated (Negative 25086-25088)
    - Molofsky Family at District 65 - (Behind them is a sign with a long list of recreational activities offered by the union), Jun 29, 1942 (Negative 1180)
    - Molofsky, Manny - with Camera [Portrait Feature], Apr 12, 1943; Nov 28, 1945 (Negative 1414; 28436)
    - Molofsky, Nat, Sergeant [Portrait Feature], Sep 24, 1945 (Negative 28407)
    - Molofsky, Sol - Farewell Party; Discharged; Molofsky Family at District 65; Sergeant Sol Molofsky - Get Together; [Capsule Biography Feature] [Portrait Feature] with Mollie Molofsky [Portrait Feature], Sep 22, 1945; Jul 18, 1942; Apr 12, 1943; Nov 28, 1945; Sep 22, 1945; Sep 24, 1945; Jul 14, 1945; undated; Feb 15, 1954; Sep 28, 1960; Jul 9, 1945; Jul 14, 1945; Jul 9, 1945 (Negative 1180; 1204-1208; 2307-2308;)
    - Mongello, John - Organizer Going to Navy [Portrait Features], Jul 30, 1962; Oct 26, 1943; Jun 16, 1958 (Negative 29314-29315)
    - Montanaro, Louis [Photographer Feature], Mar 31, 1954 (Negative 27258)